Muhammad Aiman Hakim

Software Engineering Student

A motivated, adaptable, and responsible computing undergraduate student from Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) which will utilize the professional and technical skills developed through past work experiences in this field. I have a methodical, customer-focused approach to work and a strong drive to see things through to completion.



Contact

Professional Experience

Address

Selangor, 43300

Phone

0172655375

E-mail

aimanhakimcy@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in /aimanhakimcv



2022-08 -

2022-08

Sales Assistant

Sports Direct, Melaka

- Researched new clients for sales team, inputting contact information into Salesforce.
- Helped customers locate products and checked store system for merchandise at other sites.



2019-09 -

Education



Dart

SQL

Flutter	
	Good

HTML Very Good

CSS •••0 Good

PHP Very Good Java Very Good

Bachelor of Software Engineer: Current **Computer And Information Sciences** Universiti Putra Malaysia - Seri Kembangan, Selangor Received Jabatan Perkhidmatan Awam (JPA) scholarship

- Dean's List [Semester 6 and Year 2022]
- Activities and societies: AJK Mutlimedia -Rekreasi & Alam Sekitar Kolej Canselor
- Current CGPA [3.623]

2018-06 -2019-04

Foundation: Agriculture Science

Universiti Putra Malaysia - Seri Kembangan, Selangor

2013-01 -2017-11

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM): Science

Hulu Selangor Science School - Batang Kali

UI Design 00000 Very Good

> Very Good

•••0

Good



• Gold Award - Invention, Innovation & Design



Malay

English

•••••

Excellent

Very Good

Exposition (IIDEX) 2016

- Gold Award World Young Inventors Exhibition (WYIE) ITEX 2017
- Silver Award ASPer PHYSICS EXHIBITION(APEx) 2018/2019
- First Runner Up Insurance Innovation Hackathon 2022